Bruce M. Stave Papers 2003.0054
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series III: History Department, undated, 1895-2001
  - (Box 86)
    - AAUP Files, 1990-1992
      minutes, newspaper clippings, and pamphlets,
    - University Senate Files
      minutes, notes, correspondence.
  - (Box 88)
    - U.S. Presidents CD Rom, 1994
    - History Department Files
      office files, correspondence, student files, articles, notes, and memoranda,
    - Books
      mid-20th century political non-fiction.
  - (Box 89)
    - History Department Files, 1981, 1996-1998
      memoranda, minutes, syllabi, articles, administrative records, financial documents, and newspaper clippings,
    - University Senate Files, 1999
      reports, memoranda, newspaper clippings, and correspondence,
    - Spring Weekend Newspaper Clippings
    - OHA Files
      correspondence, notes, financial documents, and memoranda,
    - Institute of Massachusetts Studies, 1983
      publication materials, correspondence, pamphlets, and articles.
  - (Box 90)
    contains unidentified photograph in frame and may include some duplicate materials
    - Oral History Files, circa 1980-1985
      photos, correspondence, journals, business cards, fliers, and publication materials,
    - History Department Files, circa 1997-2000
      student records, catalogues, pamphlets, office records, reports,
    - NEAOH Membership List, 1980
    - CT Workers, Research Notes and Correspondence
    - COH, Files and Edwin Griswold Transcripts
    - UConn Foundation Files.
  - (Box 91)
    - UConn Foundation Files, 1983-90
      newspaper clippings, financial documents, and notes,
    - Red Brick in the Land of Steady Habits Research Notes
      Photcopies: Casteen,
    - University Senate, Files and Minutes, 1986-1990
    - AHA Files, circa 1991
    - History Department Files, circa 1990
      student files, notes correspondence, newspaper clippings, fliers, reports, and pamphlets,
    - CCLU Files.
  - (Box 92)
    - History Department Files, circa 1992
      office Files, student files, financial documents, correspondence, newspapers, newsletters, and reports,
    - University Senate Files and Financial Documents, 1993-1994
    - South Africa Correspondence, 1990-1992.
  - (Box 93)
    - AAUP Files
    - NEAH Files
    - History Department Files, circa 1995
      reports, newspaper clippings, memos,
    - University of Connecticut Files, 1995-1997
      reports, newspaper clippings, memos, financial documents, pamphlets, newspapers, maps, notes, and correspondence,
    - Growth and Development Committee Files, 1996-1997
      reports, newspaper clippings, correspondence.
  - (Box 94)
    - History Department Files, Searches and Program Evaluations
      Noether Chair and others, financial, notes, correspondence, and reports,
    - Growth and Development Committee Files
      newspapers, correspondence, reports, notes.
  - (Box 95)
    - History Department Files, Reports, and Notes, 1987
    - AAUP Files
      newsletters, newspaper clippings, reports.
  - (Box 96)
    - History Department Files, 1986-1990
      pamphlets, memoranda, correspondence, notes, reports,
    - Poland Exchange Files, 1988-1989
      pamphlets, correspondence, notes, photocopies: articles,
    - Student Examination
    - CCLU Files, 1989-1990
  - (Box 97)
    - History Department Files
      - Armenian Studies
      - Judaic Studies
      - Newsletters and Correspondence
    - Journal of Urban History, Publication Materials and Research Notes, 1986-1987
    - AHA, Photography and Urban History, 1986
    - Jewish Historical Society Files
      pamphlets, correspondence
    - Student Documents
    - Unidentified Documents.
  - (Box 98)
    - NEH, Financial Documents and Office Files, 1989
    - History Department Files
      - Noether Chair, 1987-1989
        financial documents, fliers, correspondence, office files,
      - Latin American Studies, 1986-1987
        financial documents, fliers, correspondence, photocopies
      - Center for Faculty/Staff Development Files, 1986
    - Legislature Files, Photocopies and Notes, 1987
    - OHA Correspondence, 1988.
  - (Box 99)
    - History Department Files
      - Office Files, 1987-1994
        financial documents, correspondence, notes, postcards,
      - History of Science and Technology Files, 1985-1986
        correspondence, pamhplets, memoranda, notes,
      - Women's History Files, 1986-1990
        notes, newspaper clippings, correspondence,
      - Middle Eastern History Files, 1990
      - Polish-Jewish History Files, 1990-1991
        pamphlets, fliers, correspondence, notes,
    - Unidentified Files.
  - (Box 100)
    - History Department Files, 1987-1990
      correspondence, pamphlets, notes, newsletter, memorandum, reports, newspaper clippings, and fliers,
    - Academics & Athletics at UConn, Typescripts and Research Notes
      newspaper clippings,
    - Dodd Center Files, 1993
      newspaper clippings, correspondence, notes, pamphlets,
    - Student Complaints Files
      This Box May Need To Be Pulled.
  - (Box 101)
    - History Department Files, 1988-1994
      correspondence, notes, newsletters, newspaper clippings, financial documents, and minutes,
    - University Senate Files and Minutes, 1982-1984
    - NEH Files
    - NEHA Files
    - Office of Fianance & Administation Files
    - Office of Placement & Career Planning Files
  - (Box 102)
    - History Department Files
      - Office Files, 1978-80
        photocopies, correspondence, newsletters, and notes,
      - Public History Files, 1978
        photocopies, correspondence, newsletters, fliers, and pamphlets,
      - Labor Education Files, 1978-1986
        correspondence, newsletters, fliers, pamphlets, notes, newspaper clippings, reports, minutes, agendas, memoranda, and publication materials,
    - University of Connecticut Faculty Affairs Files, 1977
    - University Senate Files, 1979-1981.
  - (Box 103)
    - University Senate Files, 1978-1979, 1982-1984
    - Social Science Data Center Files
      includes pamphlets
    - History Department Files
      office files, correspondence, and reports,
    - UConn Foundation Files
      reports, memoranda, correspondence, and photocopies,
    - NEH, Memory and Immigration: Interpreting Oral History, Grant Files
    - University of Connecticut Faculty Affairs Files, 1977
    - Student Documents
  - (Box 104)
    - History Department Files, Academic Visitation Requests, circa 1990
      correspondence, journals, photocopies, and newspaper clippings,
    - Student Documents
    - AAUP Files, circa 1976
      correspondence, newsletters, notes, newspapers, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and fliers,
    - SSDC Files and pamphlets, 1976-1979
    - University of Connecticut Research Foundation Files and Financial Documents, 1971-1980
  - Urban History Conference Files, 1978-1980 (Box 105)
    correspondence, notes, syllabi, programs, newsletters, newspaper clippings, advertisments, photocopies, publications, pamphlets, and reports.
  - (Box 106)
    - Urban History Conference Files, 1978-1979
      memoranda, correspondence, notes, syllabi, newspaper clippings, 1 journal, and one book,
    - History Department Files, 1993-2000
      correspondence, notes, syllabi, advertisments, agendas, memoranda, reports, 1993-1994 faculty directory, and ephemera.
  - History Department Files, 1993-1994 (Box 107)
    correspondence, notes, advertisments, agendas, memoranda, reports, publications, pamphlets, 1993-1994 student workbook, newspaper clippings, photocopies, and maps.
  - (Box 108)
    - History Department Files, 1992-1993
      correspondence, notes, memoranda, reports, pamphlets, newspaper clippings, financial documents, student organization manuals, and newsletters,
    - COH Files, circa 1993
      catalogues, financial documents, correspondence, and ephemera,
    - Photographs and photographic materials
      some in frames, negatives,
    - Books, 20th century, political
      JFK's Profiles in Courage likely in collection already,
    - Silver Cup
      damaged - lip is bent,
    - Brass FDR Paperweight
      damaged - head broken off of base.
  - Memorabilia (Box 109)
    - Button
    - Charleston, MA Wooden Water Main Cross-Section, circa 1800
    - AAUP Placard, circa 1995
    - Chinese Dragon Doll
    - Bumper Stickers
    - Ephemera
    - Chinese Themed Calendar.
  - (Box 110)
    - University Senate Budget and Election Files, 1978-1980, 1972-1976
      financial documents, newspaper clippings, reporsts, agendas, notes, and minutes,
    - Work Study Files, Financial Documents, and Notes, 1975-1985
      This Box Must Be Pulled - student documents,
    - Urban Studies Files, 1971-1982
    - Employee Benefit Files, 1971-1975
    - Unidentified Files
  - (Box 111)
    - Department of History and University of Connecticut Files, 1971-1980
      newspaper clippings, notes, memoranda, articles, student files, and staff employment files included,
    - Urban History
      reports, correspondence, catalogues, conference papers, and grant applications,
      - NEA: City Options, Resource Files
      - Conference on the Dynamics of Modern Industrial Cities, Paper Submissions, 1979.
  - History Department Files, 1972-1982 (Box 112)
    reports, correspondence, student files, minutes, staff employment files, memoranda, and newspapers.
  - (Box 113)
    - University Senate Files: Memoranda, Correspondence, and Financial Documents
    - History Department Files
      newsletter, correspondence, personnel files, student files, and financial documents,
  - (Box 114)
    - COH Files, circa 1995
      corespondence, newspapers, newspaper clippings, reports, financial documents, and reports,
    - History Department Files, 1994-1995
      correspondence, personnel files, financial documents, reports, notes, and searches: African American Chair, and Latin American Chair,
    - University Senate Files and 1989 Racism Report, 1995-1996, 1989
      newspaper clippings, newspapers, correspondence, and photocopies,
    - History Department Files - Noether Chair Interview Transcript, 1995
    - Curriculum Vitaes, circa 1992.
  - (Box 115)
    - CCCPH Files, 1986-1991
      correspondence, notes, 1 booklet, newspaper clippings, and agendas,
    - University of Connecticut Files, circa 1990
      - Asian American Association Files
        newspaper clippings, photocopies, and correspondence,
      - Atheletics
        newspaper clippings, photocopies, fliers, and correspondence,
      - School of Business
        newspaper clippings, photocopies, fliers, reports, pamphlets, and correspondence,
    - UPA Files, circa 1990
      pamplets, typescripts, notes, and correspondence.
  - (Box 117)
    - AAUP Files, Files, 1998-2000
      business cards, financial documents, correspondence, pamphlets, newsletters, 1 cd rom, and notes,
      Note: several files significantly damaged,
    - OHR Files, 1997
      publications, interviews, correspondence, and photocopies,
    - COH Files, circa 1998
      pamphlets, correspondence, fliers, and menus.
  - University Senate Executive Committee and Committee of Three Files, 2000-2001 (Box 118)
    newspaper clippings and photocopies included.
  - (Box 119)
    - OHR Files and Surveys, 1997
      photocopies, financial documents, correspondence, and memoranda,
    - COH Files, 1997-1998
      correspondence, pamphlet, fliers, notes, memoranda, photocopies, typescripts, newspapers, publications, financial documents, and newspapwer clippings
      - South Africa Files
      - SNET Files
      - Jackie Robinson Files
        some files are duplicates from other boxes.
    - Oral History Society of England, Pamphlet, circa 1997
  - (Box 122)
    - OHA Files, 1996-1997
      correspondence, notes, financial documents, fliers, transcripts, and pamphlets,
    - OHR Files, 1996
      correspondence, notes, financial documents, fliers, reports, newsletters, newspapers, memoranda, business cards, and pamphlets,
  - (Box 123)
    - OHR Files, 1996
      minutes, notes, pamphlets, journals, correspondence.
  - History Department Files, 1992-1996 (Box 124)
    correspondence, financial documents, pamphlets, newsletters, photocopies, and notes.
  - (Box 125)
    - History Department Files, 1987-1993
      correspondence, financial documents, pamphlets, newsletters, photocopies, newspaper clippings, reports, notes,
    - AAUP Files and Questionaire, 1992-1993.
  - (Box 127)
    - History Department Files, circa 1999-2000
      correspondence, notes, clippings, pamphlets, fliers, faculty files, photocopies, business cards, and reports,
      This Box May Need To Be Pulled
  - (Box 128)
    - History Department Files, American Survey Course Notes and Resources
      newspaper clippings, and photocopies,
    - JUH Typescripts, Publications, and Correspondence, 1975-1983, 1993
    - University of Connecticut and Board of Trustees Files and Reports, 2000
  - (Box 129)
    - Dodd Center Pamphlet, 2000
    - Board of Trustees Files, 2000
      reports, newspapers, minutes, and correspondence,
    - University Publications
      University of Connecticut Laws and By-Laws, and Faculty Handbook.
  - Urban History, Reseach Notes, 1989-1994. (Box 130)
  - Urban History, Research Notes and Publications, 1984-1994. (Box 131)
  - Unidentified documents, undated (Box 132)
  - 20th Century Political and Economic Books (Box 5)
    books both fiction and non-fiction.
  - 20th Century Political and Economic Books, Newspaper clippings and Political periodicals (Box 6)
    some duplicates, largely leftist publications.
  - 20th Century Political and Economic Books and Reports (Box 7)
    some duplicates, mostly communist.
  - (Box 19)
    - Provost Papers
    - High School History Certification Files
    - Ferguson Files
    - Searches, 1987-1988
    - Offer Letters.
  - (Box 20)
    - Cox / Langer Proposal
    - Cox / CHC French Grant
    - Balanced Curriculum and Western Civilization Files
    - UMass Evaluation, 1986
    - Jackson Interview.
  - (Box 34)
    - AAUP Files